My name is Marielle Nwana and I'm an NYC-based technologist. I've spent the last four years building a deep understanding of data analysis, with a focus on technical skills. Through those experiences, I've found that I'm a self-starter who is comfortable navigating ambiguity in high-growth environments to drive key results. I'm passionate about using technology to automate manual tasks and provide users with useful tools and information.

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS .....

**Programming**Python, Java

Database & Engineering
SQL, Snowflake,
DBT, Google Cloud,
Databricks, Airflow,
Postgres

**Visualization** Looker, Tableau, Google Data Studio Site Analytics Heap Analytics, Google Analytics, Google Optimize

**Data Science** Pandas, Scikit-Learn, R, NumPy

## WORK EXPERIENCE ......

Tula Skincare / Nov 2021 - Present / Senior Growth Analyst

- Partner with Growth Marketing to track, report, and analyze new customer acquisition efforts
- Support conversion optimization through site analytics tracking and event analysis
- Advise e-commerce team on key customer and product KPIs

### Flowcode / Oct 2019 - Nov 2021 / Tech Lead - Business Intelligence

- Build out enterprise client reporting in partnership with client success managers to ensure scalable insights and analysis across 80 customers using Looker, Python and Snowflake
- Work cross-functionally to provide internal stakeholders in product, sales, marketing and finance with insights in order to understand changes in key internal metrics using Looker, SQL, and custom ETL pipelines

#### Essence Digital / May 2018 - Oct 2019

Senior Data Analyst - Machine Learning: Led research in attention signals for programmatic ad bidding and campaign optimization, created an ETL workflow for collecting data to feed client-facing dashboards, and analyzed social media data for campaign optimization research Data Analyst - Campaign Analytics: Led Analytics support for multiple campaigns amounting to over \$100 mill. of media spend. This work included building internal measurement tools for efficiency, consulting on media buying, conducting campaign tests, and working with external teams to drive campaign success

#### EDUCATION .....

Master of Science - Stevens Institute of Technology / Aug 2018 - Dec 2019

Business Intelligence & Analytics with Data Science Concentration: Coursework included experimental design, optimization and process analysis, multivariate analysis, data mining, data warehousing, social network analysis, machine learning, and web mining

# Bachelor of Science - Ohio State University / Aug 2013 - Dec 2017

Data Analytics with Business Specialization: Coursework included computational, mathematical and statistical foundations of data analytics